[EP24]
I'm gonna report you.
I saw you
instructing servants to hide prohibited drugs in the Su's house.
You also told Madame Su
that Commander Ling was killed by you.
You poisoned Lord Su in the hospital.
You also threatened Madame Su
that if she didn't die,
you would kill Su Muwan.
I saw you.
After being discovered by me,
you drove to hit me.
Fortunately, the Young Marshal protected me and I survived.
You...
You killed my son.
I'll kill you.
Grandma.
Madam.
Kill me?
do you think you're worthy?
Don't forget,
it was you
who always treated me
as a tool to bear children for your family.
Mom,
I've done well.
I gave you a grandson.
You should be satisfied.
Let me go.
Who dares to stop me?
This old woman
will die here.
Calm down.
Shen Jingshu,
if you have any complaints about the Ye family,
come at me.
Come at you?
My dear sister,
don't forget
that you've been poisoning Su Muwan
to poison Su Muwan
and spy on Ling Shenxing.
Hmph.
You're the one
who did all these.
Now you're acting like a good person.
Don't hurt her.
How ridiculous.
Su Muwan
is about to die.
You should be happy.
You always dislike her.
Although I dislike her,
she never thought about
harming my life.
But you,
you keep
making trouble everywhere.
Well said.
So well that I regret
I should have
given you more Ghost Vine.
It would have been better if you died.
You're cruel.
You're no better.
I want to know why.
The reason.
Ling Shenxing,
I've told you.
The reason is
I want wealth,
money and power.
Are you satisfied?
I want to be myself.
I don't want to fight
and scheme
in this mansion.
I want to end all this.
Am I wrong?
Ling Shenxing,
you've been standing too long
you have no idea how perilous it is
for us women
in this turbulent world.
Men
can maneuver in the officialdom
and make a fortune in business.
But what about women?
What about me?
I
was born into the Shen Family.
Since I was old enough to understand,
I was taught to please the elders
and compete with my sisters.
Every day in this big mansion,
we fight
and scheme.
How can I not want to win?
If I don't win,
if I don't win,
I'll just wait to be thrown out
like rotten vegetable leaves,
to be trampled on?
Ling Shenxing,
if I could be like you,
the Shen Family would have dominated long ago.
Do you think I enjoy these underhanded tactics?
As a weak woman,
with no strength to bind a chicken,
what else can I rely on
but scheming within the walls?
And you,
seem cold and ruthless,
but at least you have choices.
You can control the situation
with your
status,
while I can only survive in a narrow space.
In this turbulent world,
if women don't become strong,
they can only become corpses.
So,
you and Chu Nanfeng
are going to step on our
Su Family's bones to rise up?
I always thought
Chu Nanfeng was smart.
I even thought
he might become
a serious threat to me,
so I was always on guard against him.
But what's the result?
He turned out to be
a love-struck fool
who's completely useless.
He thought he could
live a stable life
in this turbulent world with his love.
How naive!
How ridiculous!
I'm so disappointed in him.
He has the ability
and ambition.
But he
traps himself
in the cage of love.
And what's the result?
He's still
at the mercy of others.
Sometimes I envy him.
At least he can live
with some fantasies.
As for me,
I've always known that
fantasies
will only lead to my downfall.
So I have to rely on myself,
step
by step.
I don't care
even if I have to step on others.
I can't go back.
Let me go.
Grandma.
Shenxing.
For my sake,
protect Ye family well.
Put down your guns!
Put them down!
Don't move!
Go to hell!
Madam!
Hang in there!
I'll get you to the hospital!
Don't worry,
I'll take care of the Ye family.
Don't worry.
Jinrou.
I'm here.
Don't live for the Ye Family.
Don't be like your grandma.
Live...
for yourself.
Madam.
Ling Shenxing.
Don't be so gloomy.
I'm fine.
I won't die so easily.
We'll meet again.
Wan.
Ling Shenxing.
Zao.
You're finally awake.
Hongxiu,
where's the Young Marshal?
What Young Marshal?
What are you talking about?
Zaozao,
this time,
let me protect you.